

Parcidio

Andre

Namibia, Windhoek, Windhoek west

parcidioandre@gmail.com

+264 81 616 5751

Reference

Timoteus Sheepo Senior Lecturer & Faculty Dean (ICT) International University of Management Tel: +264 614336178 M: +264 81 306 2832

M: +264 81 306 2832 E: t.sheepo@ium.edu.na

Benitez Kasaona Information Management ICT Service Officer NIPAM

Tel: +264 612964775 M: +264 814556087 E: bkasaona@nipam.na

SUMMARY

Software Developer with experience in coding, establishing system improvements and testing, research and helpdesk. Interested at developing software for the web and mobile devices. I consider myself a creative and dynamic person, aware of my responsibilities and willing to learn new things.

Education

Bachelor Honors of Science in Software Engineering and Development (2021): International University of Management.

Bachelor of Science in Software Development (2018-2020): International University of Management.

Namibia Senior Secondary Education Certificate (2017): Chairman Mao Zedong High School.

Skills

- Programming (Java, C++, C#, Python, Django)
- Graphics Design
- Research
- Critical thinking
- Collaboration
- Communicate effectively (English, Portuguese, Afrikaans)

Experience

Namibian Institute of Public Administration and Management (2021): ICT Technician intern.

- Recommended computer products and applications to improve productivity
- Installed and maintained company's computer systems and network
- Helpdesk
- Trained staff
- Performed data backup
- Server administration
- Web administration

International University of Management (2020-2021): Research and E-learning assistant

- System administrator of the LMS (Learning Management System)
- Assisted with office paperwork, logistic and appointment scheduling
- Assisted in the development and management of online courses
- Assisted in the formulation of research publications
- Assisted to deliver lectures

International University of Management (2020-2021): Software development intern

- Software development and process documentation
- Linux remote server operations
- Software test and deployment

Research Papers Reference

- 1. Martin Mabeifam UJAKPA, Onesmus NGHIPUNDJWA, Valerianus HASHIYANA, **Parcidio ANDRE** & Iyaloo NDEVAHOMA. (2021). An Investigation of the Use of Career Guidance App by Undergraduate Students: The Case Study of Namibia. 2021 IST Africa Conference, Virtual Conference, May, 2021. http://www.ist-africa.org/Conference2021/files/IST-Africa2021 FinalProgramme.pdf
- 2. Martin Mabeifam UJAKPA, Lorrain Pombili TUUTALENI, Iyaloo NDEVAHOMA, Gloria IYAWA, Velarianus HASHIYANA, **Parcidio ANDRE**, Nalina SURESH & Jude O. OSAKWE. (2021). Understanding Mobile Phone Use in Electricity Scarce Context: Extended TAM for Sub-Saharan African Countries. 2021 IST Africa Conference, Virtual Conference, May, 2021. http://www.ist-africa.org/Conference2021/files/IST-Africa2021 FinalProgramme.pdf
- 3. Rajesh Arora, Abraham Pendapala Ashipala, Martin Mabeifam UJAKPA, **Parcidio Andre**, Iyaloo Ndevahoma & Jacob Dapilah. (2021). Effectiveness of Auditing in Public Organizations: The Case of Ministry of Environment and Tourism, Khomas Region, Namibia. International Journal of Business Research and Management (IJBRM), 12(1). http://cscjournals.org/library/manuscriptinfo.php?mc=SIBRM1-3